segaarcade.com 2009-06-16

# Sega Amusements USA - Online Privacy Policy

| 

Home » Privacy Policy

 **Last Updated:** February 7, 2007

Sega Amusements USA, Inc. (" **Sega** " or " **we** ") respects the privacy rights of our online visitors and is committed to protecting the personal information collected about you. To further this commitment, we have adopted this Online Privacy Policy (" **Privacy Policy** ") to guide how we collect, store, and use the information you provide us at our websites [http://www.segaarcade.com](http://www.segaarcade.com/), [http://www.sau.sega.com](http://www.sau.sega.com/), [http://www.sauservice.com](http://www.sauservice.com/), [http://www.seuservice.com](http://www.seuservice.com/), [http://www.saupartsonline.com](http://www.saupartsonline.com/), [http://www.sammyusa.com](http://www.sammyusa.com/), [http://segaallnet.com](http://segaallnet.com/), [http://segaamusements.com](http://segaamusements.com/), [http://segaprizeusa.com](http://segaprizeusa.com/), [http://segatoyusa.com](http://segatoyusa.com/), and [http://www.extremehunting.net](http://www.extremehunting.net/) (collectively, the " **Site** ") which are hosted and operated from the United States.

This Privacy Policy will tell you:

  * The scope of this Privacy Policy;
  * Exactly what information Sega may collect from you online;
  * How Sega will use the information it collects;
  * Who collects the information that you disclose on the Site, and with whom such information is shared;
  * What are the consequences if you refuse to provide your Personally Identifiable Information to Sega when requested;
  * Sega's policy regarding links to websites operated by other companies;
  * How you can view, and if necessary, update or delete the Personally Identifiable Information Sega has already collected and stored about you;
  * The steps Sega takes to ensure the security, quality, and integrity of the Personally Identifiable Information it collects from online visitors;
  * The information you need to ask a question or file a complaint regarding this Privacy Policy or Sega's online information practices; and,
  * Sega's policy regarding the collection of information from children under 13.

**The scope of this Privacy Policy:**

Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to information submitted and collected by Sega online through the Site, and does not apply to information that may be collected by Sega offline. In addition, this Privacy Policy applies to Sega only, and **not** to websites maintained by our affiliates or by other companies or organizations to which we link. When you link to these websites or to any other sites from the Site, this Privacy Policy no longer applies. Sega is therefore not responsible for the content or activities provided on such sites.

By using and submitting personally identifiable information to the Site, you signify your assent to Sega's Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. If we make a material change to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting the change on the Site or in this Privacy Policy and, if necessary, give you additional choices regarding such change. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes. You can determine when this Privacy Policy was last revised by referring to the "Last Updated" legend at the top of this page. Your continued use of the Site will signify your acceptance of these changes.

**What types of information does Sega collect?**

Sega gathers two basic types of information through the Site: "Personally Identifiable Information" (or "PII") and "Non-Personally Identifiable Information" (or "Non-PII"). Personally Identifiable Information is information that identifies you as an individual; that is, your name, postal address, telephone number, e-mail address as well as any user name and password you create on the Site. PII also includes payment information, including, without limitation, your credit card number, the expiration date of your credit card, your billing address, and your shipping information (collectively, "Payment Information"). Non-Personally Identifiable Information is any other information, such as aggregated information, demographic information, IP addresses and any other information that does not reveal your specific identity.

> **(i) Personally Identifiable Information**

You do not have to provide PII to use the Site. However, in order for you to take advantage of particular opportunities provided through the Site (for example, to register to enter an online tournament or to make a purchase), we may require that you furnish PII. We collect PII from you only if you voluntarily provide it to us - for example, when you register to enter an online tournament or for a chance to win a prize, when you register to receive our newsletters, when you make a purchase through the Site or when you contact us through the Site. Please note that before you can use some of the activities above, you may be required to register and create a user name and password.

> **(ii) Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

When you visit and interact with the Site, Sega and third parties with whom Sega has contracted to provide services to Sega may collect Non-PII (for example, a catalog of the Site pages you visit). Non-PII is generally collected from five different sources: cookies, IP addresses, MAC addresses, log files and information you voluntarily provide.

> **a) Cookies**

We may use cookies on the Site. A "cookie" is a small bit of record-keeping information that sites often store on a user's computer. Cookies are typically used to quickly identify a user's computer and to "remember" things about the user's visit. For example, Sega uses cookies to keep track of your preferences and your username and password. Information contained in a cookie may be linked to your PII for this purpose. You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer, although this may affect your ability to use many of the features on the Site.

> **b) IP Addresses**

An Internet Protocol (IP) address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet. Although we do not generally collect IP addresses, we may collect and use your IP address when we feel it is necessary to protect our service, the Site, customers, or others.

> **c) Log Files**

Other Non-PII that may be collected by Sega is in the form of logs - files that record website activity, including how many "hits" a particular web page is getting (a.k.a. "navigational data"). These entries are generated anonymously, and enable Sega to gather statistics about users' browsing habits, assess overall website activity, track interest in advertised sales, and maintain website security. We also use the log file entries for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve the online services we provide you. Log files are used internally only, and may be combined with data collected via cookies to help us aggregate behavior patterns of registered users.

> **d) Other Information Collected Automatically**

When you participate in an Event (as defined below) through the Site, we may collect certain other information about you or your computer, such as your game board serial number.

> **e) Information You Voluntarily Provide**

Sega also collects Non-PII (e.g. your interests and demographic information, such as geographic location, etc.) when you voluntarily provide such information to us.

**How does Sega use the information it collects?**

> **(i) Personally Identifiable Information**

Generally, PII that we collect for a particular purpose is used only for that purpose. For example, if you email us a question, your PII will only be used to provide a response to your inquiry. Similarly, PII collected from those who register on the Site is used to provide registrants the benefits that come along with registration, which often include a subscription to our newsletter, access to the latest game news and special offers, contests, tournament prize claims and other features.

If you wish to purchase any product or service made available through the Site (each such purchase, a "Transaction"), we may collect Payment Information from you related to such Transaction, and may use such Payment Information in order to complete the Transaction and, if applicable, to fulfill your purchase. We may also provide such Payment Information to third parties as necessary to complete your Transaction (for example, to process your credit card).

In some instances, however, you may also be given the option to have your PII used for an activity or service different from the activity or service that you are requesting (for example, have your email address added to our newsletter mailing list when entering a contest). If you choose to receive these additional services, we will use your PII to provide them to you.

From time to time, we are approached by third party companies and organizations that provide products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. To extend these products or services to you, we may use your PII to send out notices on their behalf, subject to your right to opt-out (See "Can I choose how my Personally Identifiable Information is used?" below). We strive to limit the notices and communications to those that we think you would appreciate receiving.

We may use your PII to send you service announcements that tell you about updates to our Privacy Policy, changes to our online service or customer service policies, and other related service changes ("Critical Emails"). Because this information may be critical to your use of the Site, you may not opt-out of receiving these emails.

In addition, PII may be used for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve the online products and services we provide you and better meet your needs. Additionally, we may use PII that we collect to ensure that someone who is cheating is excluded, and to enforce our rights under our Terms of Service.

No matter what method we use to collect PII and no matter how we use that information, we will only collect the PII deemed reasonably necessary to fulfill your online requests and our legitimate business objectives.

> **(ii) Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

Because Non-PII collected on the Site does not personally identify you, Sega may use Non-PII for any purpose. For example, Non PII may be used for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve the online products and services we provide you and better meet your needs, and such Non-PII may also be analyzed in order to track your standing in an Event (as defined below), the popularity of certain pages of the Site, the success of our email notifications, traffic levels on the Site and other usage data, all of which helps us to improve the Site and related services and to gauge interest in the Site and Sega.

Who is collecting my information and is it shared with anyone?

> **(i) Personally Identifiable Information.**

Generally, the PII that you disclose on the Site is collected by Sega or by a service provider on Sega's behalf, and is used in accordance with the practices set forth above. Service Providers (or agents) are entities that provide support for the internal operations of the Site and who only use the PII we share with them for the purpose of carrying out the service you have requested (e.g., newsletter delivery, fulfillment of contest entries, and fulfillment of any Transactions, including processing your credit card).

We may operate sweepstakes, contests, tournaments and similar promotions, events and activities ("Events") through the Site. We typically ask you for certain PII when you enter and, if applicable, win an Event. We reserve the right to share this PII with third party sponsors of such Events (irrespective of whether they are hosted by us), or otherwise in accordance with the rules applicable to such Events. You should carefully review the rules of each Event in which you participate through the Site, as they may contain additional important information about Sega's or a sponsor's use of your PII. To the extent that the terms and conditions of such rules concerning the treatment of your PII conflict with this Privacy Policy, the terms and conditions of such rules shall govern. If you do not want your information to be collected by or shared with a third party sponsor, you can choose not to participate in those Events at the time the PII is collected.

In addition, certain PII, including your user name, town or city and state will be available to the public if you choose to participate in an Event and are featured in one of our ranking tables.

We also reserve the right to disclose your PII if we believe that we are required to do so; (a) by law; (b) to comply with legal process or governmental requests; (c) to enforce our Terms of Service; (d) to protect our operations; (e) to protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of Sega, you, or others; and (f) to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain. As an example, we may, to the fullest extent the law allows, disclose PII about you to law enforcement agencies to assist them in identifying individuals who have been or may be engaged in unlawful activities.

In addition, in the event of a merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of Sega's assets or stock (including without limitation in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings), any information collected by Sega on the Site may be transferred to its successor or assign, if permitted by and done in accordance with applicable law.

> **(ii) Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

Generally, Non-PII is collected by Sega and its vendors, and Sega may share Non-PII (which does not personally identify you) with our affiliates and with third parties for any purpose. For example, we may say a particular game title's audience is X% female and Y% male. This data is used to customize the content and advertising of the Site to deliver a better experience for our visitors. It can also help tailor Sega's products and services to meet the needs of our customers.

Additionally, Sega sends to your web browser most of the advertisements you see when you visit the Site. However, Sega may allow other companies, called third party ad servers, to serve advertisements within the Site. Please note that third party ad servers may use cookies and other technologies to, among other things, record which ads your browser has seen and which Site pages you may have been viewing when the ads were delivered. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, these third party ad servers. If you want to prevent a third party ad server from sending or reading cookies on your computer, or collecting other Non-PII about you, you must visit each of the company's websites individually and opt-out.

**What happens if I refuse to provide my Personally Identifiable Information to Sega?**

If you choose not to submit PII when requested, you may not be able to use many of the features offered on the Site. For example, if you refuse to disclose your name or email address, you may not be able to submit a question to customer service, or to participate in an Event. However, to simply browse and view certain content on the Site, you do not need to give us any PII.

**What is Sega's policy regarding links to third party sites?**

You should be aware that while you are browsing the Site, you may be directed to third party sites that are beyond our control and for which we are not responsible. Because we cannot guarantee that the privacy policies of such sites meet our high standards, we recommend that you read the privacy policy of the website to which you link before you submit any PII on such third party sites.

**Can I choose how my Personally Identifiable Information is used?**

If you do not want to receive our newsletters or other email communications (excluding Critical Emails) from Sega, please opt-out from these services at the time of registration or collection of PII. If you have opted-in and, at a later time, wish to opt-out, please click the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of your most current email from Sega. If you are experiencing problems with opting out, please contact Sega at webmaster@sau.sega.com or Sega Amusements USA, Inc. 800 Arthur Avenue, Elk Grove Village, IL 60007.

If you do not want us to share your PII with third party sponsors of Events, or with other third parties for their marketing purposes (as stated in this Privacy Policy), you may opt-out of such sharing by contacting Sega at webmaster@sau.sega.com or Sega Amusements USA, Inc. 800 Arthur Avenue, Elk Grove Village, IL 60007. Please note that opting-out of having your PII shared with such third parties may limit your ability to participate in Events. In addition, to the extent that your PII has already been shared with such third parties, you will have to contact these third parties directly to opt-out in accordance with their privacy policies.

**How can I access my Personally Identifiable Information?**

We provide you with several options for reviewing, correcting, updating or otherwise modifying PII that you have previously provided through the Site:

  1. You may contact us by email at [webmaster@sau.sega.com](mailto:webmaster@sau.sega.com).
  2. You may contact us by regular mail at Sega Amusements USA, Inc. 800 Arthur Avenue, Elk Grove Village, IL 60007, ATTN: Event Promoter.
  3. You may contact us by toll free phone at (888) 877-2669, or (877) SEGA-FUN ((877) 734-2386).
  4. You may contact us by fax at (847) 427-1065.

In each event, you must clearly indicate the information that you wish to have changed, or clearly indicate that you wish to have your PII removed from our database. We will endeavor to comply with your request as soon as is reasonably possible.

Please note that despite any removal of or change to PII requested pursuant to this section, we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes, and there may also be residual information that will remain within our databases and other records, which will not be removed or changed. We also reserve the right, from time to time, to re-contact former users of the Site. Finally, we are not responsible for informing third parties (including without limitation our third party vendors and/or third party sponsors) with whom we have already shared your PII of any changes requested pursuant to this section, or for removing information from or causing information to be removed from the databases or records of such entities.

**What safeguards does Sega use to protect my Personally Identifiable Information?**

Sega maintains appropriate safeguards that ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of the PII we collect and store about you. These safeguards include, among other things, limiting access to such data to those employees performing a legitimate business function; technical security measures, such as encryption or passwords, to prevent unauthorized access; and the storage of data on secure servers or computers inaccessible by modem.

We also have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control (i.e., maintain data quality). We also take reasonable steps to ensure that third parties to whom we transfer PII provide sufficient protection of such data.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, although we strive to protect your PII, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us through or in connection with the Site. No method of transmitting or storing data is completely secure. You acknowledge and agree that any information you transmit through the Site is so transmitted at your own risk. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with the Site is no longer secure, you must immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us in accordance with the section entitled "Contact Information," below (please note that physical mail notification will delay the time it takes for us to respond to the problem).

**Sega's Privacy Policy for Children 13 and Under:**

Sega Amusements complies with the Federal Trade Commission’s Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) that was enacted to protect the privacy and safety of children 13 and younger. COPPA specifically precludes the collection of any personal information of children without the parent or guardian’s prior consent. Personal information may include the full name, home address, e-mail address, or telephone number. Sega Amusements will not collect more personally identifiable information than is reasonably necessary to administer the activity.

When Sega Amusements knowingly seeks the personal information of children 13 and under, it will notify the parent or legal guardian of our privacy policy and obtain verifiable parental consent before collecting personally identifiable information from the child. Our only exceptions to this policy would be when we collect only the child’s first name and online contact information to (1) obtain parental consent or to provide parents with notice; or (2) respond specifically to a child’s one-time request.

When we notify parents or seek their consent, we will provide them with a copy of this policy. We also let parents know that they retain the right to review, delete and refuse to allow the collection of any personal information at all times. If the parent wishes to review, refuse further collection of, or have deleted their child’s information, they need only notify Sega Amusements’ website operator, Jeff March, by email at [privacy@sau.sega.com](mailto:privacy@sau.sega.com) or [segakids@sau.sega.com](mailto:segakids@sau.sega.com); or contact Sega Amusements by calling toll free (888) 877-2669; by fax at (847) 427-1065; or you may write to Sega Amusements U.S.A., Inc. at 800 Arthur Avenue, Elk Grove Village, IL 60007, Attn: Event Coordinator. Sega Amusements will respond to any parent or guardian’s request within 24 hours of receipt. 

Any personal information of children 13 and younger obtained by Sega Amusements will be used for internal purposes only, such as to promote other games or to notify contest winners. Sega Amusements will only share this information with third parties to promote other games. Parents also retain the right to refuse the sharing of their child’s information with third parties.

Sega Amusements U.S.A., Inc. ("Sega Amusements") is committed to protecting the privacy and security of its online visitors and to creating a safe environment for children. If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Sega Amusements’ Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@sau.sega.com](mailto:privacy@sau.sega.com) or by calling us toll free at 888-877-2669. 

**How do I ask a question or file a complaint? (Contact Information)**

If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding this Privacy Policy or our information collection practices, please contact us by email at [marketing@sau.sega.com](mailto:marketing@sau.sega.com), or by writing to us at Sega Amusements USA, Inc. 800 Arthur Ave. Elk Grove Village, IL 60007

Home | Corporate Info | Find a Distributor | Trade Shows | F.A.Q. | Contact Us | Video Games   
Redemption / Vending Games | Archive Games | Cabinet Conversion | Merchandise / Prizes   
Policies and Procedures | Privacy Policy | Terms of Service

|
